nwaonline.net 2002-06-02

# NWAonline.net Privacy Statement

### 

### Stephens Media Group Electronic Privacy Statement

#### Privacy Information

This document details the policies of Stephens Media Group ("Stephens"), www.nwaonline.net and affiliated sites, regarding Internet privacy issues.

Stephens Media Group does not currently require consumers to supply personal information in order to use the sites. However, it reserves the right to do so in the future, with or without notice, since business models and Internet technology are rapidly changing. It also does not collect any information about any child under the age of 18. 

Stephens Media Group may utilize "cookie" technology on the sites.

Stephens Media Group may perform statistical analyses of its sites to measure consumer acceptance and to gauge relative interest in various parts of the sites and to inform advertisers as to how many consumers have seen or "clicked" their advertising banners. In performance of these analyses, we will disclose information to third parties in aggregate form. 

Stephens Media Group reserves the right to change these policies at any time. Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted at the sites.

#### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY STATEMENT

No information should be submitted to or posted at NWAonline.net and affiliated sites by persons under 13 years of age. NWAonline.net does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and do not sell such information. All NWAonline.net and contests are open only to persons over the age of 18. 

If we discover that we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe NWAonline.net has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us immediately at the address listed below. 

Questions about our children's privacy policy may be directed to: Mark Hinueber, 702-383-0211 or [mhinueber@lvrj.com](mailto:mhinueber@lvrj.com).
